{
    "id": "30edea88397644bfb73db62433be44ae",
    "title": "Irregular Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There …………………………. a discussion about the most effective ways to increase productivity.",
            "description": "Arose is the simple past of arise. ",
            "answers": [
                "arose",
                "arised",
                "rised"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "New difficulties have …………………………..",
            "description": "Use the past participle form of the verb after have. Arisen is the past participle form of arise. ",
            "answers": [
                "arose",
                "arised",
                "arisen"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I was ………………………….. by the loud noise.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "woke",
                "awoke",
                "awakened"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………. her when we played chess yesterday.",
            "description": "Beat is the past and past participle form of beat.",
            "answers": [
                "beat",
                "beated",
                "beaten"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………………….. down to pick up the coin.",
            "description": "Bent is the past simple form of bend. ",
            "answers": [
                "bend",
                "bent",
                "bended"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The robber was …………………………. to a tree.",
            "description": "Bound is the past simple form of bind. ",
            "answers": [
                "bind",
                "binded",
                "bound"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I was ………………………….. by the dog.",
            "description": "Bitten is the past participle form of bite. The passive forms are made with past participles. ",
            "answers": [
                "bite",
                "bit",
                "bitten"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The dog …………………………… me while I tried to restrain him.",
            "description": "Bit is the past participle form of bite. ",
            "answers": [
                "bite",
                "bit",
                "bitten"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The injured man ……………………………. to death.",
            "description": "Bled is the past simple form of bleed. ",
            "answers": [
                "bleed",
                "bled",
                "bleeded"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A breeze ……………………………… gently.",
            "description": "Blew is the past simple form of blow. ",
            "answers": [
                "blow",
                "blowed",
                "blew"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You are the ……………………………. one.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "chose",
                "chosen",
                "choosen"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "That laptop ……………………………… me six hundred dollars.",
            "description": "Cost is the past simple and past participle form of cost. ",
            "answers": [
                "cost",
                "costed"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}